koostube.com 2009-06-20

# We give you porn tube for free! Porno videos in KoosTube - Privacy Policy

KoosTube's Privacy Policy

### Information Collection and Use by KoosTube.com:

KoosTube.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the KoosTube.com service. KoosTube.com might also collect other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.  
Email addresses are used for the purposes to send notifications related to the service. a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on KoosTube.com with each other through the KoosTube.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members.   
From time to time, KoosTube.com , may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on KoosTube.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.  

### Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members:

KoosTube.com members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. KoosTube.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations, KoosTube.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders. 

### Links:

KoosTube.com contains links to sites. KoosTube.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on KoosTube.com. 

### Correcting/Updating or Removing Information:

KoosTube.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info. 

### Third Party Advertising:

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by KoosTube.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by KoosTube.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Security:

KoosTube.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords KoosTube.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on KoosTube.com, please contact us a admin@KoosTube.com. 

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information KoosTube.com Collects:

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, KoosTube.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by KoosTube.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the KoosTube.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. KoosTube.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of KoosTube.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

### Submitted Material:

KoosTube does not control the uploaded material, therefore, any privacy or Copyright Infringement complaint from anyone who claims he has rights to any material presented on KoosTube.com and that the material presented is a violation of privacy or copyrights, the said material will be immediately removed. 

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy:

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.   
KoosTube.com cares deeply about online privacy If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at admin@KoosTube.com.
